nativly.com 2017-06-04

# Nativly

We respect your privacy, and we want you to know how we use the information you provide to us. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to your use of our website located at www.nativly.com (the “Site”) operated by Nativly Group Ltd, 1906 El Camino Real Menlo Park, CA 94027*(“us” or “we”).

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting our Site and using our Customer or Partner Service (as defined in Terms of Use and herein collectively referred to as “Services”), you agree that your information, including your personal information, will be handled as described in this Privacy Policy, which is incorporated by reference into the Terms of Use. 

### Information We Collect

We collect personal information and non-personal information from and about you when you use the Services. Specifically, we collect information: (1) directly from you, such as when you contact us, submit a post or submission (2) from third parties, and (3) automatically, as you move through our Site such as Site usage, browser types, IP addresses or device IDs, and other data, as discussed below.

**_Information We Collect Directly From You._** We request information from you when you post a comment or submission, or contact us. Depending upon the particular activity, we may request the following information from you: your name, email address, zip code, gender, age range and so on.

**_Information We Collect About You From Third Parties._** From time to time, we may add the capability to log into our Site through different social networking sites. If you log into our Services through a social networking site, we will request your name and certain basic information. We also may request certain permissions from you, which vary based on the social networking site. For information about how the particular social networking site may disclose your information, including any information you make public, please consult their privacy policy. We have no control over how a third party social networking site uses or discloses the personal information that you provide to it. We store the information that we receive from the social networking site along with other information that we collect from you or receive about you. 

**_Information We Collect Automatically._**  We use cookies, web beacons, Flash, and other automated devices to collect information about you when you visit our Site and our Application. Specifically, we collect the following information about your use of our Site via these technologies: your browser type and operating system; web pages you view; links you click; your IP address; your interaction with the Site; length of time you are logged in to our Site; and websites visited before our Site. With regard to the Application, we may collect your mobile device ID; location and language information; device name and model; operating system type, name and version; your activities within the Application; and the length of time that you are logged into our Application. We will request your information before we collect your location. Please see the section “Use of Cookies, Flash Cookies, HTML5, Web Beacons, and Other Tracking Devices” below for more information about our use of these tracking devices. We may use the information gathered through these methods in anonymous or aggregated form to analyze ways to improve our Services. This information may be associated with your username and may be combined with other information, including personal information that we collect about you. 

**_Location Information._**  We may also may collect your location. We may combine your location information with other information that we have collected about you. 

### Use of Cookies, Flash Cookies, HTML5, Web Beacons, and Other Tracking Devices

When you interact with our Services, we strive to make your experience easy and meaningful. We or our third party service providers use cookies, web beacons (including clear GIFs), Flash LSOs, and similar technologies to track user activity and collect data about our Site, Services, and our users. As stated above, we may combine this data with the personal information we have collected from or about you.

**_Cookies._**  We use browser “cookies” on our Site. Cookies are a website’s way of remembering who you are. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer’s hard drive or stored temporarily in your computer’s memory. There are two kinds of cookies, and we use both types of cookies on our Site: “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies. Session cookies are deleted when you close your browser. Persistent cookies remain on your computer and retain information for later use tomorrow, next month or whenever they are set to expire. We use cookies to help us to identify account holders and to optimize their experience on our Site. Also, we will use cookies to monitor and maintain information about your use of this Site. Most Web browsers accept cookies automatically. You can delete cookies manually or set your browser to automatically delete cookies on a pre-determined schedule. If you decline to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in certain features of this Site.

Other companies that place advertising on our Site also have the ability to assign their cookies to you. You can opt out of the collection of certain information about you by many online advertisers. Please see the section below entitled “Advertising” for additional information. 

**_Use of Flash Cookies and HTML5._**  Our Services enable the use of the Adobe Flash Player. Your use of the Adobe Flash Player generates “flash cookies” (also known as “persistent identification elements” or “local shared objects”). The Adobe Flash Player (and similar applications) uses flash cookies to remember user settings, preferences and usage in a manner similar to the browser cookies referenced above. Flash cookies can store more information than browser cookies and are managed through a different interface than the one provided by your Web browser. You can control the degree to which you accept flash cookies by accessing your Adobe Flash Player management tools directly through the settings manager for Adobe Flash, located at http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html. (Users running the Windows operating system can generally view flash cookie files in this folder: \Documents and Settings\\[username]\Application Data\Macromedia\Flash Player. Users running the Apple operating system can generally view flash cookie files in this folder: /users/[username]/Library/Preferences/macromedia/Flash Player. Flash cookies, or LSO files are stored typically with an “.SOL” extension. If you do not allow flash cookies on your computer, you may not be able to take advantage of or participate in certain features of our Services. 

HTML is the software language used for building most of the sites on the internet. Some HTML5 code may allow your responses to advertising and other activities to be monitored across websites, and for such information to be stored on your computer or mobile device and accessed by others you do or have done business with. We assess user activity information stored through this feature of HTML5. As with cookies, other companies that place advertising on our Site may have the ability to access information using this feature of HTML5. We do not control and are not responsible for any such access or for their use of information obtained. 

**Web Beacons.**  Our Web pages or e-mail messages may contain a small graphic image called a Web beacon, which is sometimes also called a “clear gif,” that allows us to monitor and collect certain information about our users, such as the type of browser requesting the Web beacon, the IP address of the computer that the Web beacon is sent to and the time the Web beacon was viewed. Web beacons can be very small or invisible to the user, but, in general, any electronic image viewed as part of a Web page or email, including HTML-based content, can act as a Web beacon. We may use Web beacons to count visitors to our Web pages or to monitor how our users navigate our Site, and we may include Web beacons in email messages in order to count how many of the messages we sent were actually opened or acted upon. We use Web beacons to compile aggregate statistics about our Site and our marketing campaigns. 

**_Analytics._**  Each time a visitor comes to the Site or uses our Application, our servers collect information, including, for example, the visitor’s domain name (e.g., the website that you came from), referral data (e.g., depending on your browser, the address of the last page or series of pages you visited prior to clicking through to our Site), and browser and platform type. We also count, track and aggregate each visitor’s activity as part of our analysis of general traffic flows at our Site (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Site, etc.). We collect some of this data directly, and we also engage third party service providers (e.g., Google Analytics) who use the technologies described in this section, to collect this information and to assist us with our analytics. 

### Security of information

We make all reasonable efforts to protect your information. However, no website, Internet transmission, computer system or wireless connection is completely secure. We cannot guarantee that unauthorized access or disclosure, hacking, data loss or other breaches will not occur. Your use of the Site and our Services is at your own risk.

We cannot and do not ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

### Use of Your Information

We use your information, including your personal information, to provide our Services to you and for the following purposes:

  * To communicate with you, to respond to your inquiries, and for other customer services purposes;
  * To provide information that you have requested to receive from us;
  * To tailor the content and information that we may send or display to you, and to otherwise personalize your experiences while using our Services;
  * To improve our Services;
  * For research purposes;
  * For marketing and advertising purposes; for example, we may send you emails about new features of our Site as well as about our products and services, as well as products and services of third parties, that we believe would be of interest to you;
  * To better understand how users access and use our Services, both on an aggregated and individualized basis.

### Sharing Information

We may provide information, including your personal information (collectively, “information”), to non-affiliated and affiliated parties for a variety of purposes as described in this section and throughout this Privacy Policy.

**_Affiliates and Non-Affiliated Third Parties._**  We may disclose your information to affiliates and non-affiliated companies when we believe their products or services may be of interest to you, so that they can contact you with offers. If you are a California resident, you have a right to obtain information about this sharing; please see the Special Notice to California Consumers below. If you respond to an offer and provide information directly to another company, that information will be subject to their privacy policy, not this Privacy Policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly. We are not responsible for the manner in which other businesses collect or use your personal information.

**_Third parties providing services on our behalf._** We may engage third parties to perform services in connection with the operation of our business. Examples of these services include: (a) distribution of marketing and promotional material; (b) website evaluation and analytics; (c) fulfilling magazine, newsletter or other subscriptions; (d) data collection, storage, management, analysis and, where applicable, cleansing, and (e) any other services designed to assist us in maximizing our business potential. These third parties may have access to information about visitors to our Site and our Application, including personal information, for the purpose of performing their duties and functions.

**_Investigations and security._** We may release information about you when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, in response to a subpoena or other legal process, or to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Site, Application, and applicable laws. We may also disclose such user information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of us, or any of our respective affiliates, business partners, customers or others.

**_Aggregate Information._**  We may disclose aggregated user statistics to third parties for a variety of purposes, including describing our services to prospective partners and other third parties, such as advertisers, and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Examples of such non-personal information include the number of users who visited this Site during a specific time period or purchased a specific product through this Site.

**_Surveys._**  We may from time to time conduct voluntary surveys of visitors to the Site to obtain aggregate demographic information about them. Such information may be compiled and shared in the aggregate with advertisers and other third parties.

**_Business Transfers/Bankruptcy._**  If we are acquired by or merged with another company, if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another company, or we re-structure our corporate group by moving assets or shareholdings to affiliates or parents, or third parties, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected from you as it is considered to be an asset of ours.

### Advertising

We may provide third-party advertisers with information about your usage of our Site and our Services on an aggregated basis.

### Special Information for California Consumers

California residents may request a list of all third parties to which we have disclosed certain personal information about you for the third party’s marketing purposes. You may make one request per calendar year. In your request, please attest that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response to you.

### Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of children is important to us. We do not collect or maintain information from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our Services is structured to attract anyone under 13. If you are under the age of 13, you are not permitted to use our Services. If you are aware of anyone under the age of 13 using our Site, please notify us. Upon confirmation, we will terminate any account that user may have, and we will eliminate any personal information we may have obtained from that user.

### Unsubscribe and Data Removal Policies

If you would like to remove any date held by us, you can send an email requesting removal to [info@nativly.com](mailto:info@nativly.com)

If you no longer wish to receive promotional emails from us, please follow the opt-out instructions in the text of the email. Please note that it may take up to ten days to process your request. Please also note that if you opt-out of receiving promotional emails from us, we may continue to contact you with via email with service related communications.

### Revisions to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, update, add to, discontinue, remove or otherwise change any portion of this Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, at any time. When we amend this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “last updated” date located at the top of this Privacy Policy. For changes to this Privacy Policy that we consider to be material, we will place a notice on the Site by revising the link to read as “Updated Privacy Policy” for a reasonable amount of time. By providing information to us or using our Services in any way after this Privacy Policy has been revised, you consent and agree to the revised Privacy Policy. The most current version of this Privacy Policy will be available on the Site and will supersede all previous versions of this Privacy Policy.

### Choice of Law

This Privacy Policy, including all revisions and amendments thereto, and any disputes arising from or relating to this Privacy Policy or your use of our Services, is governed by the laws of BVI, without regard to any conflict or choice of law principles that would require application of the laws of another jurisdiction.

### Questions about our Privacy Policy

If you have any further questions or concerns about our privacy policies and use of personal information, please send them to [info@nativly.com](mailto:info@nativly.com)

*Address mentioned here above is only operational and not legal/registered of the company. Such information is confidential and contains only in Insertion Order.
